Guide to the Gelman Library Assistant University Librarian for Collections records, 1951-1995 RG0108
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Gelman Library Associate University Librarian for Collections and Scholarly Communications records
1951-2010
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Gelman Library. Office of the Assistant University Librarian for Collections
RG0108
40 Linear Feet
Material in this collection dates between 1951 and 2010, and includes correspondence, budgets, reports, photographs, publications, office files, blueprints of Gelman Library, strategic planning notes, and a video cassette.
Acquisition Information
Materials were transferred to the University Archives by the Associate University Librarian for Collections Services.
Historical or Biographical Note
The George Washington University's Melvin Gelman Library opened in 1973. Before the Gelman Library (which received its current name in 1980), the University Library was located in Lisner Hall, formerly Lisner Library. When the University moved to Foggy Bottom in 1912 from its location on 15th and H Streets, N.W., the first library was located in the original Lisner Hall, the former St. Rose's School for Orphaned Girls, between 20th and 21st Streets on G Street. Other libraries include the Virginia Campus Library (established n 1990), and the Mount Vernon Campus Eckles Library (under GW control since 1997). Together, these three libraries form the Gelman Library System (GLS).
The Library is headed by a University Librarian, who oversees: the Assistant University Librarian, Administration, Development, and Personnel; Associate University Librarian for Collections and Scholarly Communication; Associate University Librarian for Information Technology; Associate University Librarian for Public Services; Directors of the Mt. Vernon and Virginia Campus libraries, and the Manager of GLS (Gelman Library System) Financial Operations.
The Assistant University Librarian for Collections was renamed as the Associate University Librarian for Collections Services in the mid-1990's. In this configuration, the position oversaw the operations of the Special Collections Department, the Collections Management Services Department, Acquisitions Department, Slavic, East European and Asian Reading Room, and the Collection Development Group.
In 2007, the Associate University Librarian for Collection Services, Caroline Long, retired and the Gelman Library undertook a two-year reorganization. The position was reconfigured as the Associate University Librarian for Collections and Scholarly Communications. The position oversees Collection Development, the Special Collections Research Center, the Global Resources Center, the Preservation Department, the Materials Budget Unit, and the Gifts and Exchange Unit.
N.B. This history note was written in 2005 and updated in 2010.
Collection Scope and Content
The majority of this collection comes from the tenure of Assistant Univeristy Librarian for Collections Caroline Long (circa 1994-2006), and also includes documents which she had inherited from her predecessors, including Christopher Filstrip. One file dates from the tenure of Assistant Librarian for Collections Benita Vassallo (file is dated 1989). This collection contains correspondence, budgets, reports, photographs, publications, office files, blueprints of Gelman Library, strategic planning notes, and a video cassette. The material dates from 1951 to 2006, and was transferred to the University Archives by the Associate University Librarian for Collections Services.
Collection Organization
Collection: Organized into eight series: Series 1: Correspondence; Series 2: Subject files; Series 3: Allocations Task Force files; Series 4: Renovation project files; Series 5: Statistics; Series 6: WLN conspectus files; Series 7: Workflow Implementation Team project files, and Series 8: Ad Hoc Committee on Publications file.
Series: Series 1 is arranged chronologically. The remaining series are arranged alphabetically.
Access Restrictions
This collection is closed to research for 25 years from date of record creation, with the exception of Series 5, which is open to research.
Photographs; Finance; Librarians; Melvin Gelman Library; Publications; Foggy Bottom (Washington, D.C.); Washington (D.C.); Catalogs, Card; George Washington University; George Washington University. Library
- Correspondence, RG0108 Series 1
  - Chronological file: external, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Chronological file: external, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Chronological file: internal [1 of 2], 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Chronological file: internal [2 of 2], 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Subject files, 1967-2006; RG0108 Series 2; 0.5 Linear Feet
  - Academic excellence [1 of 4], 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Academic excellence [2 of 4], 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Academic excellence [3 of 4], 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Academic excellence [4 of 4], 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Access Services Unit (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Accreditation, 1983-2006
    - Accreditation, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Accreditation - Art Therapy, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Accreditation - Exercise Science and Tourism, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Accreditation - Government and Business Administration, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Accreditation - Graduate School of Education and Human Development, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Accreditation - Music, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Accreditation - Public Administration, 2000 August (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Accreditation - School of Business and Public Management, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Accreditation - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Accreditation - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Accreditation - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Accreditation - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences (ABET/CSAB), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Accreditation - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences: ABET, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Accreditation - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences: CSAB (1992/1993 - 1996/1997), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Accreditation - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences: ABET (1997/1998 - 1999/2000), 2001 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Accreditation - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences: CSAB, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Accreditation - Teacher Preparation and Special Education, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Accreditation - Urban and Regional Planning, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Acquisitions, 1993-2006
    - Acquisitions trips (faculty), 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Acquisitions, 1995-2005 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Acquisitions: evaluation of vendor guidelines, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Acquisitions - exchanges, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Acquisitions: ILL to Acquisitions Task Force [1 of 2], 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Acquisitions: ILL to Acquisitions Task Force [2 of 2], 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Personnel, 2004-2006 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      Access Restrictions
      Access to this folder restricted until 2078. Access requires the written authorization of the Associate University Librarian for Collections and Scholarly Communication.
    - Acquisitions - reorganization, 2004-2006 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Acquisitions: rollover FY2002 to FY2003, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Acquisitions: rollover FY2003 to FY 2004, 2002-2004 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Acquisitions: rollover FY2004 to FY 2005, 2003-2005 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Acquisitions - sale of serials, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Acquisitions - serials consultant, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Acquisitions: USBE, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Administrative group, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Administrative group, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Administrative group, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - ALADIN, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - ALADIN ledger, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Allocation formula, 2001-2006
    - Allocation formula - area studies, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Allocation formula spreadsheets [1 of 2], 2001-2005 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Allocation formula spreadsheets [2 of 2], 2001-2005 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Allocation formula spreadsheets: applying allocation formula, 2001-2006 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - American Women's Composers, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Annual reports, 1992-2000
    - Annual report, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Annual report, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Annual report, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Annual report, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Annual report, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Annual report, correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Annual report [1 of 2], 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Annual report [2 of 2], 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Annual report [1 of 2], 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Annual report [2 of 2], 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Annual report, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Approval plan, 1978-1990
    - Approval plan: Blackwell's North America: background materials [1 of 3], 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Approval plan: Blackwell's North America: background materials [2 of 3], 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Approval plan: Blackwell's North America: background materials [3 of 3], 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Approval plan: Blackwell's North America: correspondence/memos, 1981-1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Approval plan: Blackwell's North America, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Approval plan: Blackwell's North America (historical): coverage and cost studies, 1975-1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Approval plan: Blackwell's North America (historical): coverage and cost studies, 1980-1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Approval plan: Blackwell's North America (historical): printouts/sales returns (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Approval plan: Blackwell's North America (historical): printouts/profiles [1 of 3], 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Approval plan: Blackwell's North America (historical): printouts/profiles [2 of 3], 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Approval plan: Blackwell's North America (historical): printouts/profiles [3 of 3], 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Approval plan: Blackwell's North America (historical): reports to libraries, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Approval plan: general (historical): Choice [1 of 2], 1978-1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Approval plan: general (historical): Choice [2 of 2], 1978-1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Approval plan: general (historical): criteria/procedures (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Approval plan: general (historical): forms, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Approval plan: general (historical): NEBS printouts/profiles, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Approval plan: general (historical): worldwide, 1970-1990 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Archivist/archives proposal [1 of 2], 1985 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Archivist/archives proposal [2 of 2], 1985 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Associate University Librarian assistant, 1975-2000 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Association of Research Libraries application [1 of 3], 1997 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Association of Research Libraries application [2 of 3], 1997 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Association of Research Libraries application [3 of 3], 1997 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Association of Research Libraries 75th anniversary: Celebrating Research materials, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes 3 CD-ROMS.
  - Blackwell's Book Services, 1999-2004
    - Blackwell's Book Services, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Blackwell's Book Services, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Blackwell's Book Services, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Blackwell's Book Services, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Blackwell's Books Services. Approval plan, 2006 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Blackwell's Book Services. Approval plan thesaurus: alphabetic subject arrangement, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Blackwell's Book Services. Approval plan thesaurus: hierarchical subject arrangement, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Blackwell's Book Services. Approval program coverage and cost study, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Blackwell's Book Services. Approval program coverage and cost study, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Blackwell's Book Services. Approval program coverage and cost study, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Blackwell's Book Services. Approval thesaurus non-subject parameters, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Series titles blocked on BBS-US approval/firm database [1 of 5], 2002 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Series titles blocked on BBS-US approval/firm database [2 of 5], 2002 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Series titles blocked on BBS-US approval/firm database [3 of 5], 2002 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Series titles blocked on BBS-US approval/firm database [4 of 5], 2002 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Series titles blocked on BBS-US approval/firm database [5 of 5], 2002 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Series titles blocked on BBS-UK approval/firm database [1 of 4], 2002 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Series titles blocked on BBS-UK approval/firm database [2 of 4], 2002 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Series titles blocked on BBS-UK approval/firm database [3 of 4], 2002 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Series titles blocked on BBS-UK approval/firm database [4 of 4], 2002 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Budget, capital, 1996-2002 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Budget, collections, 1967-2006
    - Budget, collections: history [1 of 2], 1988-1996 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Budget, collections: history [2 of 2], 1988-1996 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Budget, collections: history, fiscal reports, 1983-1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Library budget, books, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Library budget - books (special funds), 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Library budget - books (special funds), 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Library budget - books, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Library budget - books, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Library budget - books, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Library budget - books (special funds), 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Library budget - books, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Budget, collections: correspondence, memos and reports, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Budget, collections: correspondence, memos and reports, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Budget, collections: correspondence, memos and reports, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Budget, collections: correspondence, memos and reports, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Budget, collections: correspondence, memos and reports, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Budget, collections: correspondence, memos and reports, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Budget, collections: correspondence, memos and reports, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Materials budget reports: National Endowment for the Humanities funds [1 of 2], 1987-1991 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Materials budget reports: National Endowment for the Humanities funds [2 of 2], 1987-1991 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Budget, collections: pre-paid subscription renewal invoices, 1990-1994 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Budget, collections, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Budget, collections, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Budget, collections [1 of 2], 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Budget, collections [2 of 2], 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Budget, collections [1 of 2], 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Budget, collections [2 of 2], 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Budget, collections: allocations, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Budget, collections, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Budget, collections: allocations, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Budget, collections: infusion, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Budget, collections, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Budget, collections: allocations, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Budget, collections, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Budget, collections: allocations, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Budget, collections: allocations: spreadsheets - special, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Budget, collections: allocations: new fund codes, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Budget, collections: allocations: collections expenditures, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Budget, collections: allocations: additional allocations, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Budget, collections: allocations: allocations by school, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Budget, collections: allocations: miscellaneous documents, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Budget, collections: allocations: memos, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Budget, collections: allocations: approvals, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Budget, collections: allocations: firms, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Budget, collections: allocations: standing orders, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Budget, collections: allocations: subscriptions, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Budget, collections: allocations: new journals, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Budget, collections: crib sheets, 1996-2005 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Budget, collections, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Budget, collections: outline, etc., 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Budget, collections: electronic resources, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Budget, collections: ledger, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Budget, collections: allocations, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Budget, collections: allocations: "deals", etc. done, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Budget, collections, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Budget, collections: budget situation - information for subject specialists / campus, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Budget, collections: outline, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Budget, collections: account balances, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Budget, collections: cancellation ideas, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Budget, collections: ledger, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Budget, collections: "R" funds, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Budget, collections: allocations [1 of 2], 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Budget, collections: allocations [2 of 2], 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Budget, collections: allocations: GENX, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Budget, collections: allocations: "deals", etc. - done, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Budget, collections: allocations: ledgers, spreadsheets, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Budget, collections, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Budget, collections: outline, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Budget, collections: electronic resources, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Budget, collections: ledger, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Budget, collections: prices for resources, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Budget, collections: meeting with Elliot School of International Affairs, 2000 February 3 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Budget, collections: "R" funds, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Budget, collections: allocations, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Budget, collections: allocations: spreadsheets, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Budget, collections: approval plan, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Budget, collections: cost of materials, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Budget, collections: e-resources, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Budget, collections: general, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Budget, collections: ledger, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Budget, collections: outline, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Budget, collections: "R" funds, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Budget, collections: allocations, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Budget, collections: allocations: spreadsheets, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Budget, Gelman, 1983-2000
    - Budget, Gelman, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      Contains correspondence, memos, and reports.
    - Budget, Gelman: correspondence/memos, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Budget, Gelman: reports, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Budget, Gelman: correspondence/memos, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Budget, Gelman: endowments, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Budget, Gelman: reports, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Budget, Gelman [1 of 2], 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Budget, Gelman [2 of 2], 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Budget, Gelman: increased enrollment, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Budget, Gelman: wage hour budget, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - CAPCON (OCLC), 1976-2006
  - CAPCON (OCLC), 1976-2003 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - CAPCON (OCLC): CAOS union list, 1984-1990 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - CAPCON (OCLC): MUTRS reports, 1997-2004 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - CAPCON: OCLC usage and cost [1 of 3], 1995-2008 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - CAPCON: OCLC usage and cost [2 of 3], 1995-2008 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - CAPCON: OCLC usage and cost [3 of 3], 1995-2008 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Chadwyck-Healey American monograph program [1 of 3], 1991 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Chadwyck-Healey American monograph program [2 of 3], 1991 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Chadwyck-Healey American monograph program [3 of 3], 1991 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Chadwyck-Healey Carnegie Peace Pamphlets collection microform project, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Chadwyck-Healey American Cumulative contents index, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Chadwyck-Healey American 19th century, 1987-1993 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Collection development/management
    - Background materials: articles [1 of 2], undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Background materials: articles [2 of 2], undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Background materials: book price/publication industry statistics, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Background materials: depreciation, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Guidelines and policies, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Procedures and functional support, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Collection analysis project [1 of 2], 1982 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Collection analysis project [2 of 2], 1982 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Collection analysis, 1982-1999 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Collection analysis: bibliography and index checking, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Collection assessment [1 of 2], 1989-2001 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Collection assessment [2 of 2], undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Collection assessment 2 [1 of 2], 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Collection assessment 2 [2 of 2], 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Approval plan, 1989-2005 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Collection management training, 1987-1992 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Collection use, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Core collections, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Replacements, 1995-2001 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Serials prices, no. 1 [1 of 3], 1989-2004 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Serials prices, no. 1 [2 of 3], 1989-2004 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Serials prices, no. 1 [3 of 3], 1989-2004 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Serials prices, no. 2 [1 of 3], 1988-2004 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Serials prices, no. 2 [2 of 3], 1988-2004 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Serials prices, no. 2 [3 of 3], 1988-2004 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Collection Development Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Collections annual report, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Collection Development Group, 1994-2006
    - Collection Development Group binder [1 of 4], 1999-2002 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Collection Development Group binder [2 of 4], 1999-2002 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Collection Development Group binder [3 of 4], 1999-2002 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Collection Development Group binder [4 of 4], 1999-2002 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Collection Development Group meetings [1 of 3], 1999-2002 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Collection Development Group meetings [2 of 3], 1999-2002 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Collection Development Group meetings [3 of 3], 1999-2002 (Box 21, Folder 6)